{
    "subject": "resource/Pfizer_UK",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Pharmaceutical_industry",
    "human_readable": "Pfizer UK operates in the Pharmaceutical industry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9551298022270203,
            "question": "What industry does Pfizer UK operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7127623558044434,
            "question": "Does Pfizer UK operate globally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6314302086830139,
            "question": "What is Pfizer UK known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6182014346122742,
            "question": "What types of products or services does Pfizer UK offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5738304257392883,
            "question": "Who are the major competitors of Pfizer UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48674923181533813,
            "question": "Does Pfizer UK conduct research and development in the UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47742095589637756,
            "question": "What is Pfizer UK's impact on the UK economy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47699302434921265,
            "question": "What are some of Pfizer UK's major initiatives or campaigns?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42837807536125183,
            "question": "How does Pfizer UK contribute to public health?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.368222177028656,
            "question": "How large is Pfizer UK's workforce?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pfizer UK operates in the Pharmaceutical industry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8014_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Pfizer UK contribute to public health?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8014_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Pfizer UK's major initiatives or campaigns?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8014_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Pfizer UK's impact on the UK economy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8014_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8014_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"Pfizer UK\" operates in the pharmaceutical industry. This is mentioned in several documents, including the first one, which states that Pfizer has worked within the UK since 1952 and supports the NHS and other healthcare organisations across the industry developing solutions to improve care and patient outcomes.\n\nAdditionally, document #39 mentions that Pfizer sells its products through wholesalers, retailers, hospitals, individual provider offices, clinics, government agencies, and pharmacies, indicating that it operates in the pharmaceutical industry. Document #104 also confirms this by mentioning that Pfizer is one of the world's leading innovative biopharmaceutical companies."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided indicate that Pfizer is a multinational pharmaceutical and biotechnology corporation, which supports the statement that Pfizer UK operates in the Pharmaceutical industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}